{
    "subject": "resource/ALGOL_58",
    "predicate": "ontology/influencedBy",
    "object": "resource/Plankalk\u00fcl",
    "human_readable": "ALGOL 58 was influenced by Plankalk\u00fcl.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800917506217957,
            "question": "How did Plankalk\u00fcl influence the design of ALGOL 58?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9658488631248474,
            "question": "Besides ALGOL 58, what other languages might have been influenced by Plankalk\u00fcl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9302963614463806,
            "question": "Describe the relationship between Plankalk\u00fcl and ALGOL 58."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.894705057144165,
            "question": "What is the connection between ALGOL 58 and Plankalk\u00fcl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8675678372383118,
            "question": "Name the influential precursor to ALGOL 58."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7212659120559692,
            "question": "What programming language was influenced by Plankalk\u00fcl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4709584414958954,
            "question": "ALGOL 58's development was shaped by what earlier work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46300050616264343,
            "question": "Which early computing language is considered a predecessor to ALGOL 58?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45323657989501953,
            "question": "What was the impact of Plankalk\u00fcl on programming language evolution?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42665863037109375,
            "question": "Which language drew inspiration from Plankalk\u00fcl's concepts?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=ALGOL 58 was influenced by Plankalk\u00fcl.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4771_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the impact of Plankalk\u00fcl on programming language evolution?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4771_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which early computing language is considered a predecessor to ALGOL 58?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4771_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=ALGOL 58's development was shaped by what earlier work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4771_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4771_83.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"ALGOL 58 was influenced by Plankalk\u00fcl.\" Specifically, it mentions that Konrad Zuse built Plankalk\u00fcl and that ALGOL 58, which was designed with most of his work (implying some influence), never acknowledged the influence of Plankalk\u00fcl on its own development."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}